https://freshening.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We know that you care about your personal data and how it is used. We want you to trust that Freshening uses your personal data carefully. We want to let you know how we do that, including what information we collect, how we use and protect it, and how you can decide what we do with it. Our main goal is for you to understand how we use your information to better improve our content, products, advertisements, and services.
What we collect
Information directly given to us from you
Information collected when you visit our site, contact us, use our products or view our advertisements
Information collected from other companies who have obtained your consent to share or sell it or have ensured that other companies from whom they have received your information can share it with them and, in turn, with us and/or other companies
We may combine any and all of this information to help create better products, services, and consumer experiences.
What we do with it
Create better products, services and customer experiences for you
Share information about the products that you seem interested in
Help us run our sites and services
How and when we share your information
With your consent, your information may be disclosed to the following parties:
Third-party service providers: for them to send you offers or ads that we believe you may be interested in
Legal disclosure: if required by the law or government authorities
How we protect your personal data
Investing in cyber security measures
Access to your information is only permitted to authorised employees and agents
Your rights
Obtain clear and transparent information on how your personal data is used
Access to update your personal data
Opt out of marketing notifications and subscriptions
Contacting us on the use of your personal data
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy notice, please kindly contact us. Freshening Industries Pte. Ltd and our organisation’s Data Privacy Offer can be contacted at 4 Loyang Link, Singapore 508895, or by email info@freshening.com.sg
Shopping cart
close
send
0
X
Welcome to Freshening
0
Home
